<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Annelise Koster&#39;s Blog for dasc1104</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Annelise Koster&#39;s Blog for dasc1104</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hotel Analysis</title>
      <link>/2020/12/07/hotel-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/07/hotel-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Hotel Analysis  Introduction The first dataset I chose was the Hotel Booking Demand dataset from Kaggle.com, this dataset is originally from the article Hotel Booking Demands Datasets, written by Nuno Antonio, Ana Almeida, and Luis Nunes for Data in Brief, Volume 22, February 2019. Thomas Mock and Antoine Bichat are responsible for cleaning the original data. This dataset contains booking information for two hotels but since the hotels mentioned are real hotels any data pertaining to customer or hotel identification has been deleted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 11:11:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Annelise Koster a Junior Data Science major at the University of Arkansas. I keep myself busy with schoolwork, an internship at my church and mountain biking. I also enjoy reading - A Girl of the Limberlost, The Kitchen Counter Cooking School, and Educated are some of my favorite books. I created this blog as an assignment for one of my programming classes and intend to use it to showcase various projects I work on throughout my school and work career.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
